Mental Health Association in New York State, Inc. (MHANYS) Records apap131
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D/ART), 1988-1998; 9; 0.5 cubic ft.
  D/ART (Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment) was a program of the National Institute of Mental Health in which MHANYS participated in the 1990s. The program involved mainly distributing literature and other information aimed at increasing public awareness of the problem of depression. For example, MHANYS prepared a translation of an already existing booklet on depression into Russian and distributed it to Russian-speaking people in New York State. This series mainly consists of literature prepared by the National Institute of Mental Health on Depression, and correspondence regarding the "Community Partners" national conferences of D/ART participants.
  - D/ART Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 1)
  - Depression, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 2-3)
  - Depression, 1991 (Box 1 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 4-6)
  - Depression, 1992 (Box 1 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 7-9)
  - Depression, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 10-11)
  - Depression, 1993 (Box 1 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 12-17)
  - Depression, 1994 (Box 2 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 1-3)
  - Depression, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 4-11)
  - Depression, 1998 (Box 2 (9-Depression Awareness, Recognition and Treatment (D), Folder 12)
- Parent Support, 1991-1999; 10; 0.66 cubic ft.
  The Parent Support series includes documents related to MHANYS programs aimed at providing support to parents with psychiatric disabilities or parents of children with psychiatric disabilities, especially in relation to enhancing families. Includes Families Together, a publication by MHANYS for families of children with special emotional, social, and behavioral needs; Forum - presentations related to providing support to parents with psychiatric problems; a proposal for MHANYS Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support (PPDS) program aimed at helping people with psychiatric disabilities who have become parents to raise their children; documents regarding New York State's Vocational and Educational Activities for Students with Disabilities (VESID) program; and external publications and reports on family issues.
  - Children and Adolescent Service Training Program, 1994 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 1)
  - Families Together, 1995; 1996 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 2)
  - Needs and Gaps in Service to Parents, 1992 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 3)
  - Parent Support Network, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 4)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 5)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, 1991 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 6)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 7)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, 1994 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 8-15)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, 1995 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 16)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, Information Packet, 1996 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 17)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, Presentation, ca. 1999 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 18)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, Proposal, 1993 (Box 1 (10-Parent Support), Folder 19-21)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, Provider Survey, 1999 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 1)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, Provider Survey, 2000 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 2)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, Quarterly Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 3)
  - Parents with Psychiatric Disabilities Support, Training, 1999 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 4)
  - Resources, 1993 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 5)
  - Supportive Family Training, ca. 1993 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 6-7)
  - VESID, 1993 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 8)
  - Working With Parents, 1998 (Box 2 (10-Parent Support), Folder 9)
- Mental Health Information Center, 2000-2001; 11; 0.17 cubic ft.
  The Mental Health Information Center is a MHANYS program created in 2000 as a successor to the Self Help Clearinghouse to respond to inquiries and handle library, information handling, and archival responsibilities. Included are summaries of calls received and fact sheets.
  - Real People, Real Stories, 2000 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 1)
    Description of a video library of stories of efforts to overcome discrimination.
  - Calls to MHIC, Summary, 2000 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 2)
  - Calls to MHIC, Summary, 2001 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 3-4)
  - Fact Sheet, Postpartum Depression, 2001 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 5)
  - Fact Sheet, Coping With Disaster and Trauma, 2001 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 6)
  - Fact Sheet, Helping Children Cope With Disaster and Trauma, 2001 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 7)
  - Fact Sheet, Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder, 2001 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 8)
  - Fact Sheet, When You Need to File a Complaint Against a Health Care Provider or Facility, 2001 (Box 1 (11-Mental Health Information Center), Folder 9)
- Self Help Clearinghouse, 1990-1996; 12; 2 cubic ft.
  The MHANYS Self Help Clearinghouse (SHC) Program was funded by the New York State Office of Mental Health to enable people with mental illness to pursue self-help and mutual aid efforts. This program involved the support of local self-help clearinghouses and distribution of information on self-help and mutual aid.
  - Administration, 1990-1995; 12.1; 0.15 cubic ft.
    The Administration subseries includes documents regarding the Alliance Education, Advocacy and Social Center, Syracuse, budget information on SHC and other MHANYS programs, a survey of self-help and mutual aid groups, and consultant information, and a job description for the director of Mental Self Help Clearinghouse.
    - Alliance Center, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 1)
    - Broome County Self-Help Clearinghouse, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1993 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1994 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 7)
    - Clearinghouse Survey, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 8)
    - Consultants, 1992 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 9)
    - Consultants, 1994 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 10)
    - Consumer Network Advocacy Center-Long Island, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 11)
    - Director's Job Description, 1994 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 12)
    - Goals and Objectives, 1994 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 13)
    - Goals and Objectives, 1995 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 14)
    - Letterbook, Theresa Bonner, 1994 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 15)
  - Contracts, 1990-1992; 12.2; 0.15 cubic ft.
    The Contracts subseries includes correspondence between the New York State Office of Mental Health (OMH) and MHANYS regarding a contract for establishing the SHC; a request for proposal from OMH regarding Self Help Programs and the resulting MHANYS proposal to operate SHC; and correspondence regarding evaluation by MHANYS of local SHC programs.
    - Contracts, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 17)
    - Contracts, 1992 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 18)
    - Contracts, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 19)
    - Proposal to New York Office of Mental Health, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 20-26)
    - Proposal to New York Office of Mental Health, 1992 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 27)
    - Proposal Evaluation, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 28)
    - Proposal Information, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 29)
    - Request for Proposal, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1996; 12.3; 0.15 cubic ft.
    The Correspondence subseries is mainly to or from Theresa Bronner, MHANYS Self-help Clearinghouse coordinator, regarding local self help clearinghouses, provision of information about mental health services, and other SHC matters.
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 32-33)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 34-36)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 37-39)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 41)
  - Reports, 1990-1996; 12.4; 0.65 cubic ft.
    The Reports subseries includes Quarterly Reports of MHANYS Self Help Clearinghouse Project, expense reports of regional self-help clearinghouse, activity reports to OMH, and other correspondence related to performance of SHC contract.
    - Quarterly Reports, 1990-1995 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 42)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 43)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1992 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 44-54)
    - Quarterly/Monthly/Yearly Reports, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 55)
    - Quarterly/Monthly/Yearly Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 56)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 57)
    - Regional Financial Reports, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 58)
    - Regional Proposals, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 59)
    - Reports, 1990 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 1-3)
    - Reports, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 4-5)
    - Reports, Summary, 1997 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 6)
  - Subject Files, 1990-1996; 12.5; 1 cubic foot
    This subseries includes a database listing of self help organizations, dual diagnosis documents regarding a training course for dealing with people who have co-occurring mental illness and substance abuse, and housing and independent living material. This includes an agreement between MHANYS and a participant in the SHC, Housing Opportunities Made Easier (H.O.M.E.) regarding local provision of service and proposal by Associated Independent living centers of NY (AILCNY) to New York OMH to establish a self help clearinghouse. In addition, there is correspondence about an education conference regarding Lifelong Learning for Adults with Disabilities, correspondence related to the Growing Wiser Program of mental health for elder citizens, evaluation sheets for monitoring the effectiveness of the SHC program, local SHC records, correspondence related to legal services in connection with SHC, correspondence regarding grants from MHANYS to local SHC groups for purchase of library materials, information regarding use of the Internet by SHC program, correspondence and other documents regarding Schizophrenics Anonymous training program for SHC participants, information regarding teleconference on self help issues, guide to selection of self help methods developed by MHANYS and MHA- Ulster County library lists, studies, surveys and evaluations, documents related to work of student interns for SHC, external studies on the self help process, and use of internet for self help.
    - Database, Undated (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 7-9)
    - Dual Diagnosis, 1994 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 10-12)
    - Education Conference, 1992 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 13)
    - Elderly, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 14-15)
    - Electronic Empowerment Model, Internet Self Help, 1999 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 16)
    - Evaluation, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 17)
    - Fulton Montgomery County Self-help Clearinghouse, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 18)
    - Fulton Montgomery County Self-help Clearinghouse, 1992 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 19)
    - Housing Opportunities Made Easier, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 20)
    - Housing Opportunities Made Easier, 1992 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 21)
    - Independent Living Center, Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 22)
    - Legal Services, 1993 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 23)
    - Library Grants, 1993 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 24-25)
    - Long Island Self Help Clearinghouse, 1992 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 26-27)
    - Memos, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 28)
    - Participants, 1990 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 29)
    - Online/Internet, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 30)
    - Publicity, 1992-1994 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 31-33)
    - Rockland County Self-help Clearinghouse, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 34-35)
    - Schizophrenics Anonymous, 1996 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 36-39)
    - Self Help Live, 1992 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 40-44)
    - Self Help Models, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 45)
    - Shelf List -- list of books in MHANYS Self Help Clearinghouse Library, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 46)
    - Status reports, 1996 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 47)
    - Student Interns, 1992 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 48)
    - Studies, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 49-50)
    - Survey, 1990 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 51-53)
    - Technical Assistance Materials, 1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 54)
    - Teleconferences, 1993 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 55-57)
    - Ulster County Self-help Clearinghouse, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (12-Self Help Clearinghouse), Folder 58-60)
- National Mental Health Association, 1962-1991; 13; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series holds documents related to MHANYS's parent organization, the National Mental Health Association. Includes correspondence, manuals, annual reports, publications, and related material.
  - Annual Reports, 1968; 1989-1990 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors' Manual, 1965 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 4)
  - NMHA Position Papers, 1992 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 5)
  - President's Handbook, 1969 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 6)
  - President's Handbook, 1970 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 7)
  - Survey of State Divisions -- Summary of Activities of State Mental Health Association, 1991 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 8)
  - Role of Affiliates, Undated (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 9)
  - Planning, 1990 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 10)
  - Reports prepared by NMHA on mental health issues and NMHA organizational topics, 1962 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 11)
  - Publications, 1969-1973 (Box 1 (13-National Mental Health Association), Folder 12-14)
- Programs, 1981-2001; 14; 1.17 cubic ft.
  - Business Advisory Council, 1986-1996; 14.1; 5 folders
    The Business Advisory Council was made up of business leaders called on to advise MHANYS on issues related to employment of persons who have experienced mental illness, to be a communication link between the private sector and mental health professionals, and to make businesses aware of the valuable human resources available through mental health rehabilitation agencies. This series includes mission statements, program and proposal documents, correspondence, and information on awards dinners sponsored by the council.
    - Business Advisory Council, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 1)
    - Business Advisory Project, 1993 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 2)
    - Business Advisory Partnership, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 3)
    - Vocational Awards Dinner, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 4)
    - Vocational Awards Dinner, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 5)
  - Children's Issues, 1989-1999; 14.2; 0.15 cubic ft.
    This series includes correspondence, conference documents, program proposals, and program documents regarding managed health care programs for children; family preservation programs; juvenile justice programs; educating students, especially in grade school, about the nature of mental illness; and support for parents with mentally illnesses or children with mental illness.
    - Children's Mental Health Education, 1993 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 6)
    - Children's Mental Health -- mental health services for children with mental illness, and for their families, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 7)
    - Children's Mental Health, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 8-9)
    - Children's Mental Health, 1996 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 10)
    - Children's Public Education, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 11)
    - Children's SSI Program, Cuts, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 11)
    - Family Preservation Proposal -- reducing length of stay of children with emotional problems in foster care environment, 1997 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 12)
    - Justice for Juveniles, 1999 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 13)
    - Managed Mental Health Care for Children with Psychiatric Disabilities, Conference, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 14)
    - Managed Mental Health Care for Children Conference, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 15)
    - Parent Support -- proposal for federal contract to provide support to families in the neighborhood setting through collaboration by MHANYS with Families in New York State, Inc., 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 16)
    - Quest Conference -- conference designed and planned by parents with severe behavioral, social or emotional issues, 1994 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 17)
    - Remember the Children -- poster sold for fundraising, 1989 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 18)
  - Consumer Issues, 1981-1994; 14.3; 2 folders
    This subseries includes contract information, presentations, proposals and other documents regarding MHANYS programs for empowerment of consumers and dialogue between consumers and providers of mental health services in New York State.
    - Consumer Empowerment, 1981 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 20)
    - Consumer-Provider Dialogue, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 21)
  - Jail Diversion, 2001; 14.4; 1 folder
    The jail diversion project was a MHANYS program for diverting from jail those persons arrested who suffered from mental illness. Included is news clipping about the project.
    - Jail Diversion, News Clipping, 2001 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 22)
    - Jail Diversion Collaboration Project, ca. 2001 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 22)
  - Managed Care, 1995-1997; 14.5; 2 folders
    This subseries includes correspondence and other documents relating to a proposal made by MHANYS to the American Psychological Foundation in 1997 to help integrate mental health care in private and public managed care systems.
    - Contract Proposal, 1997 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 23)
    - Mental Health and Managed Care, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 24)
  - Open Mind, 1993; 14.6; 5 folders
    The Open Mind subseries includes correspondence and other documents related to the organization by MHANYS of a network of self help groups in New York State to use Open Mind, an electronic information network developed in California for the distribution of mental health related information.
    - Open Mind, 1993 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 25)
  - Panic Education, 1993-1994; 14.7; 0.1 cubic ft.
    The Panic Education subseries includes documents related to a contract received by MHANYS in 1993-1994 to perform services under the National Institute of Mental Health Panic Disorder Education Program.
    - Panic Disorder Education, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 26-37)
  - May is Mental Health Month, 1990-1994; 14.8; 0.05 cubic ft.
    The May is Mental Health Month subseries includes material distributed by NMHA to MHANYS and by MHANYS to its affiliates for use during the May campaign of public information on mental health issues.
    - May is Mental Health Month, 1976 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 38)
    - May is Mental Health Month, 1978 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 39)
    - May is Mental Health Month, 1990 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 40)
    - May is Mental Health Month, 1994 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 41)
    - May is Mental Health Month, Kit, 1994 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 42)
    - May is Mental Health Month, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 43)
    - May is Mental Health Month, Kit, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 44)
  - Recipient Empowerment, 1993-1994; 14.9; 3 folders
    The Recipient Empowerment subseries includes documents related to a MHANYS program about empowering recipients of mental health services. Included is Empowerment, the newsletter of the MHANYS Recipient Empowerment Program, and related documents.
    - Empowerment, 1993 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 45)
    - Project Proposal for Managed Care Recipient Training, 1994 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 46-47)
  - Rural Health, 1995; 14.10; 3 folders
    The Rural Health subseries includes documents related to MHANYS programs on rural mental health issues and to the Rural Council, a New York State Department of Health council on rural health issues.
    - Rural Council, 1995 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 48-50)
  - Supported Education, 1991; 14.11; 2 folders
    The Supported Education subseries includes documents related to the reintegration into post-secondary education of young adults with serious mental problems, prepared by Four Winds Center, Saratoga Springs, New York.
    - Supported Education Programs, 1991 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 51)
  - Sexual Abuse, 1994-2000; 14.12; 0.15 cubic ft.
    The Sexual Abuse subseries inclues documents related to a proposal by MHANYS in response to a request for proposals (RFP) from the New York State Department of Health for a project on sexual assault and trauma issues and establishment of a rape crisis center and documents related to the Sexual Assault/Mental Health Project of MHANYS and the New York State Coalition Against Sexual Assault, Inc.; documents concerned with other MHANYS activities related to sexual abuse; the Task Force Networker, a newsletter of the Sexual Assault/Mental Health Project of MHANYS and the New York State Coalition Against Sexual Assault, Inc.; and the proceedings of a forum on sexual abuse survivors held at the College of St. Rose in Albany, New York.
    - Expanding the Bridges, Sexual Assault and Sexual Abuse Training, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 52)